Are you getting this?
Can you hear me?
Goat's milk.
Here, drink this.
It's too dark.
Hi, I'm Hinaka.
I bought something.
As you can see from the previous videos...
It's shot with a cell phone.
So there's the sound of the wind.
I was worried that the sound of the wind might be included in the video, or that it might be knocked over by the wind, or something.
I was worried about all kinds of things with the cell phone.
So this time
My bangs are a little bad.
I bought a gople this time.
There's no vacancy yet.
Here you are.
I didn't know what to buy.
So I bought the newest one.
Oh, that's cool.
You want to take it with you?
Oh, wow!
That's awesome.
It's cool.
What? - Cool.
What is this? What's in it?
I don't know.
What's this?
This.
It's, like, a charging cord or something.
Oh, no, it's Type C.
Is that it?
Charging?
No?
It's a battery.
I think it's a battery.
I bought batteries, too.
I don't know, I don't think they last that long.
I don't think they lasted that long.
What are these too? What?
What?
I know what this is.
It's a camera.
What? It's nice.
It's cute.
I'm gonna open it.
I want to put some film on it.
What?
Is it okay to open this?
It's not something you can just buy without knowing what you're doing.
I don't know, I don't...
Oh, wait a minute, don't you think you get it? This is...
Oh, oh, and, and, and, and, and, and...
This is it, isn't it?
This is it.
Oh.
It looks like it's facing the wrong way.
It's definitely something.
It's definitely different.
What?
So...
What's this?
What is it?
Oh, I see. There's like a library of instructions.
Oh, there it is.
Here it is! Here it is!
Oh, this is it.
It's supposed to go on your helmet.
Right?
Mm-hm-hm-hm.
This one looks good.
And I bought this...
I bought this one too.
Already
this
So cute!
Oh, this one stands up.
It's so cute!
It stretches.
Like this.
And that one.
You put this on this.
That's interesting.
Interesting.
Something's different.
Yes, so the GoPro is here, too.
I'm going to go to Reaokun's now.
Grandma's house, grandma's house
My mom's grandma's house is in Kanagawa.
So I'd like to go to my grandma's house. I'll check it out. I'll take some pictures with the GoPro.
Is it working? Can you hear the sound?
I don't know, I don't know anything about the settings on the GoPro.
I wonder what the picture quality is like.
Is it good?
It can't be bad.
It's amazing, you know, like a bus driver.It's amazing, isn't it, bus drivers?
Truck drivers.
They're so cool.
I'd love to be a bus driver.
Why are they so big? How do they turn? It's like...
That's amazing.
I kind of want to try it.
I'm a little curious.
Okay, everyone, listen up.
There's a cow.
Tell that to the camera.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Is it dangerous?
Kanagawa.
Wow, that's amazing.
They sold something.
They were selling cucumbers on the way here.
No one was there.
Sold by someone else.
Wait a minute.
I really want to buy some.
Well, they're out of cucumbers.
I should've bought some.
Sorry for the short notice.
Oh, Leo!
It's the first baked milk I've ever had in my life.
You're saying that, aren't you?
Mysterious sudden postrecording.
The sound is a little...
There's a lot of sounds mixed in.
He's speaking now.
He's saying, "This is delicious.
Oh, excuse me, it was a recording.
The guy who came to dinner with us... who was at the restaurant... said this is chicken breast.
He said this is chicken breast.
Here you go. Say thank you.
That's great, Leg. He loves it.
That's great. That's great.
That's great. Hey, Leo.
Hey, I'm glad you like it. I want to come back.
I'd like to come back here... a little bit at a time, a little bit at a time.
Bye-bye. Thank you.
Bye-bye.
Thank you.
Okay.
Take care.
See you next week.
Oh, my goodness. Be quiet.
My dinner.
Here it comes.
Bon appétit.
Can I have one?
One for you, brother. Three for me.
I don't want three.
Keep it up.
Fold it in, fold it in, fold it in, fold it in.
Delicious.
Bon appétit.
Yeah, it's good.
I didn't exercise today.
No.
Delicious.
It's good. It's good.
It's so good.
Wow, this is delicious.
Really? Oh, good.
Thanks for your help.
The guys are taking care of Leo now.
Hey. - Leo?
Leo?
You're happy again, aren't you?
I'm happy.
Hey.
Hey, wait.
There it is.
Ah!
Aah! Aah!
I'm going to eat, boy.
See you later.
Okkun, see you later.
Hi!
On the way back, Leo and I
We came to Enoshima.
Is it too dark to see?
Enoshima Island
It smells like a lot of things.
For Eric.
You know what I'd like to do?
I want to take a picture with Neo.
I wanted to take a picture of him with these sunglasses on.
I wanted to take a picture.
Oh, it's already dark.
It's dark again...
Take this with you.
Is there any place you can see Enoshima from here?
Not anymore.Oh, it's gone.
I wanted to take a picture with Leo, but it's already dark!
Oh boy.
That thing is awesome.
Can we get a picture?
Oh, there's a bird.
Do you see it?
Can't you see it?
There's something in the mist.
It's beautiful.
There's a fisherman.
I'd like to take a picture of you and Leo.
And I want to take a picture of you wearing sunglasses.
What? I can't do that.
Will I catch a cold?
I want to take a picture
I'd love to take a picture of you and Leo.
Good night.
You really don't scare me a little bit, do you?
Mmm.
mmm
Okay, bye-bye.
Bye-bye.
bye-bye!
Okun bye bye
That's all for Enoshima.
♪♪
♪